Guide to the Department of History, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1940-1987; Accession 1997-A-080
  - Howard Fellows, October 19 deadline, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Maps, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Films, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Project Eli Computers, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Council of Masters, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Minorities completing Ph.D. degree and entering job market, January 1986 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Office furnishings, HGS basement and 305 Crown St., Undated (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Personnel, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Honorary degrees, 1981-1986 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Prize teaching fellowships, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Prizes, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Teaching assignments for 1985-1986 (Provost's request) (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Teaching assignments and scheduled hours (for Provost's office), 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 68A)
  - Budget for teaching by Yale graduate students, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Budget for teaching by Yale graduate students, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Teaching assignments and scheduled hours (for Provost's office), 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Strike hours, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Andrew W. Mellon foundation fellowships, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Samuel and Ronnie Heyman prize for outstanding scholarly publication or research by junior humanities faculty, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Revisiting the Rose report, numbers of men and women in selected History departments, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Clare Booth Luce visiting professors, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Curriculum review committee, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Yale College; standing, special and appointments committees, 1982-1989 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Saint Andrews society scholarship, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Librarian, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - African studies, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Departmental committees and representatives, 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Undergraduate prizes, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Lecture courses for 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Undergraduate major statistics; classes of 1986 and 1987 (based upon fall term enrollment), 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - History course enrollments, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 86A)
  - Prizes, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Prizes, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Prizes, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Prizes, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 89A)
  - Retirement policies, 1979-1989 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Federal legislation regarding mandatory retirement, December 3, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Telecommunications project, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Bourne Medal, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Retirements, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Retirement party, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Statement on alcohol policy, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Quorum members, 1983-1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - History departmental committees, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Lectures, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Lectures, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Lectures, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Lectures, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Lectures, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Poisition of lecturer, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Leaves, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Leaves, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Leaves, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Leaves, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Leaves, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Leaves, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Leave lists, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Twentieth-century diplomatic, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - British History, Turner-Stuart and twentieth-century, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Eighteenth-century British History, 1980-1984 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Colonial History, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 24A)
  - Sub-committees, Hapsburg and Soviet Russia, October 7, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Latin American History, 1978-1984 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Modern European, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Afro-American History, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Yale handbook, policies, and procedures, 1981-1986 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Korean History and culture, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - History lunch attendant, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Department meeting, January 29, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Meeting, full professors, February 12, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Full professors meeting, February 18, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Department meeting, February 26, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Full professors, March 5, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Department meeting, April 2, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Full professors meeting, April 9, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Full professors meeting, May 21, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Department meeting, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Department meeting, annual review of graduate students, May 28, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Graduate programs of other Universities, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Leaves of absence, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - AHA meeting, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Economic History, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Undergraduate History, major-problems, course of study, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Yale Historical publications committee, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Undergraduate, History 89, reading list, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - History department appointments, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Jobs and fellowships applications, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Applications for jobs at Yale, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Candidates for doctoral degrees, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Candidates, American History, 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Young men to see, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Candidates; European History, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - General discussions on men and appointments, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Candidates for jobs at Yale for European History, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Teacher complaints, May 5, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - American History candidates for Yale job, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Possible appointments to Yale, 1956-1958 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Possibilities for appointments at Yale, 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Old possibilities for appointments in American History, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Appointments possibilities, miscellaneous notes, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Candidates for jobs, 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - History of diplomacy, foreign affairs, and international relations, 1957-1961 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - History of Education, 1957-1961 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - India, 1958-1962 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Graduate enrollments, History, 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Graduate program in History; admissions and fellowships, 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Graduate school, History and miscellaneous, 1959-1962 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Fellowships in History, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Graduate programs in History, 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Catalogue statements, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Graduate student statistics, 1959-1961 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Amherst Memorial fellowship, 1957-1960 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Yale's Ph.D. History Reconsidered, March 10, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - History graduate enrollment statistics, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Applications for graduate funding and fellowships, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Prize fellowships, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Graduate fellowships, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Appplications from foreign students, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Placements, job recommendations, 1960 September-December (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Placement, job recommendations (parts I and II), 1961 January-July (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
  - Placement, job recommendations (parts I and II), 1961 Deptember-December (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
  - Placement, job recommendations (parts I and II), 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
  - Job openings to pursue, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Yale candidates for jobs, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Offices, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Offices, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Office assignments, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Office space and assignments, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Space and office moves, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - History department space report, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Office space, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Office assignments, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Office furnishings and moving costs, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Offices, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Office furnishings for 135 Prospect St., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Furnishings for chairman's office, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Offices (assignments) old, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Budget, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - New Yale movie, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Woodrow Wilson memorial commission, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence with Corporation, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Visitors expected, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Yale summer high school, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Committee on Education (parts I and II), 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 32-33)
  - Graduate and professor prizes, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Research fellow correspondence, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Research time inquiry, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Report of summer activities, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - News from other History departments, 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Russian History, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Yale reports, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - European History (Graduate), 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Social Science committee, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Undergraduate prizes, 1965-1968 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - History prizes (Mr. Mellon), 1962 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - History prizes (Mr. Mellon), 1961 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - History prizes (Mr. Logan), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - History prizes (Mr. Logan), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - History prizes (Mr. Rodriguez), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Yale History series and old department records, 1882-1938 (Box 15)
  - Mr. Pierson's era-misc. I, 1955-1957 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Mr. Pierson's era-misc. II, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Mr. Pierson's era-misc. III, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Mr. Pierson's era-misc. IV, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Department reports, miscellaneous mimeography chairmanship of Mr. Pierson I, 1958-1962 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Department reports, miscellaneous mimeography chairmanship of Mr. Pierson II, 1958-1961 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Office of Univeristy Development, re: Griswold and Seymour chairs, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Chinese History and Civilization, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Far Eastern (F.E.) plans and personnel, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Department of History of Science and Medicine, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - History of Science and Medicine (H.O.S.A.M.), possible appointments, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - History of Science, possible appointments, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - History of Science and Medicine (H.O.S.A.M.), courses and course of study, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - History of Science and Medicine (H.O.S.A.M.), minutes of governing board, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - History of Science, general correspondence, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - History of Science chair, 1958-1960 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - History of Science, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - History of Science lectures, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Promotion of History of Science, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Yale Medical School 150th, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Directed Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Latin American Studies, etc..., 1962 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Law School, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Medieval Studies, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Other departments: Political Science, and Economics, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Freshman year, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Statements on new chairs in History, 1957-1961 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - History of Education, 1959-1962 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Professor Funds, 1959-1962 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Seymour, Charles and House, Edward M., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Asakawa chair, 1960-1962 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Asakawa, K., 1949 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Alumni, endowments, speeches, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Development of Cornell speech, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - U.S. Steel Foundation, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Foundation, directory, and center, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Letters (part I), 1960-1966 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Letters (part II), 1960-1966 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes, teaching fellows, and appointments, 1967-1972 (Box 17, Folder 1A)
  - Undergraduate History program (parts I and II), 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
  - Graduate History Program, miscellaneous, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Andrews Society and graduate advisory committee, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Faculty data, salary, and appointments, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Job openings, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - European appointments committee, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Graduate school History admissions correspondence, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Faculty appointment applications and History department data, 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Prizes, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Leaves, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Leaves, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Leaves, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Leaves, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Junior faculty leaves, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Teaching fellows, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Post-doctoral (P-D) fellow applications, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Post-doctoral (P-D) fellow applications, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Junior faculty considered during 1965-1966 for 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - English History appointments committee, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Letters from University officers, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Yale seminars in modern journalism, Poynter Fellowships, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - 00001-87LA, closed, office machines, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - 00001-87KA, closed, equipment and furnishings (Cost of $500 or more), 1983 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - 00001-68HA, closed, data processing, software purchases, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - 00001-66XA, closed, equipment, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - 00001-65FA, closed, B, P, A, MA, maps, 1982-1986 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - 00001-62DA, closed, wages, other Yale students, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - 00001-66FA, closed, data processing supplies, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - 00001-69EA, closed, PF, honoraria, 1982-1986 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - 574A-31-00001 account printouts (monthly), 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - 00001-70BA, closed, equipment maintenance, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - 00001-70DA, closed, data processing, equipment maintenance, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - 00001-87MA, closed, data processing equipment, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - IBM personal computer, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Medieval search H-T, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Eighteenth Century British History slot, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - B, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - C-D, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - G-H, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - I-J-K, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - L, withdrew application, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - M, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - N-S, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - T-W, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Medieval search, A-G, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Renaissance History, responses regarding possible candidates, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Responses to letter regarding possible candidates, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - 00001-86, telephone-telegraph, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Pending 09-DA, (submit E.R.), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - 00001-82AA, office supplies, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - 00001-68PA, closed, SA, printing-publications, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - 00001-68ZA, closed, SA, miscellaneous services, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - 00001-66KA, closed, M/S films, slides, tapes and recordings, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - 00001-85BA, closed, SE, advertising and publicity, 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - 00001-65MA, closed, miscellaneous acquisitions, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - 00001-66DA, closed, food service supplies, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - 00001-66YA, closed, miscellaneous materials (i.e., flowers, hand tools, etc...), 1986 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - 00001-68FA, closed, catering and meals, 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - 00001-68GA, closed, data processing services, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - 00001-68NA, closed, SA, photocopy services, 1982-1987 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - 00001-69ZA, closed, PF, other professionals, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - 00001-70CA, closed, ERM, data processing equipment rental, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - 00001-75AA, closed, departmental renovations (i.e., keys, etc...), 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - 00001-79AA, closed, travel - domestic, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - 00001-79BA, closed, travel - foreign, 1983-1987 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - 00001-79FA, closed, entertainment - other, 1981-1986 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - 00001-79EA, closed, entertainment - business, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - 00001-85AA, closed, moving and relocation, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - 00001-82FA, closed, subscriptions - books, periodicals, newspapers, 1983-1987 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - 00001-82GA, closed, postage, 1982-1987 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - 00001-85CA, closed, subsidies to special programs, publications, government, educ. organiza., 1985 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - 00001-85HA, closed, dues and memberships (educational, business, athletic associations or societies), 1983-1987 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - 00001-85ZA, closed, miscellaneous expenses, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - 00001-86AA, closed, telephone rental, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - 00001-86DA, closed, telephone - tolls, 1981-1984 (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - 00001-96FA, closed, CR, professional services, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - 00001-96HA, closed, CR, photo copy service, 1981-1987 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - 00001-96MA, CR, closed, telephone services, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 00001-96ZA, CR, other services, (IDT), 1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Expenses for graduate student affairs, 1974-1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - XEROX, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Search, assistant professor of U.S. History; specialization in History of Spanish speaking people, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - History-Humanities search, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - History/Humanities search, A-B, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - History/Humanities search, C, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - History/Humanities search, E, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - History/Humanities search, F-L, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - History/Humanities search, K-L, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - History/Humanities search, M-O, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - History/Humanities search, R, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - History/Humanities search, S-W, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - British search committee A-G, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - British search committee H-L, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - British search committee M-W, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Modern French Social History (Merriman), 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - British search committee, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Modern British History expenses, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - British and European Intellectual History, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Connecticut statute on disclosures of personnel files, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Buckley amendment, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Report of departmental committee on teaching fellows, Lowenstein papers, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Elderhostel course, summer, "The American People and the Sea", 1981 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Office of business/industry relations, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Hajo Holborn prize, Undated (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Arthur F. Wright fund, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - S and H grant, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - University of London, Institute of historical research, 1966-1982 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Allan Nevins prize, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Frederick W. Beinecke prize, 1970-1977 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - M.A.s alphabetical letter by degree, Undated (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - M.A.s by date, 1891-1969 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Alphabetical list of Ph.D.s, year/director/dissertation title, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Addresses of History Ph.D.s and M.A.s as of December 1977 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Graduate school brochures, student guide and application brochure, 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Andrews Society, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Graduate school, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Yale alumni fund, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Yale graduate school alumni fund, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Graduate school alumni fund, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Yale alumni records regional list, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Master's degree program, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Yale alumni magazine and journal, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Graduate school solicitation of gifts, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Graduate school alumni fund (parts I and II), 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
  - History department, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Graduate affairs, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Graduate affairs, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Graduate affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Graduate school, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Graduate school, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - History graduate affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Graduate school, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - M.Phil. degree, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Lists of History Ph.D.'s, 1947-1962 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Combined B.A.-M.A. program, December 18, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Summer term, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Summer term, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Summer term, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Committee on the summer term, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Undergraduate affairs, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Undergraduate affairs, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Undergraduate affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Yale College, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Yale College, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - History undergraduate affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Yale College, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Course to be taught in 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Course offerings, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Undergraduate affairs (parts I and II), 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - Yale College, 1964-1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Yale College, projected course enrollments, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate statistics, 1960-1966 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Advanced placement, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Results of departmental exams, 1957-1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Old departmental exams to be shown to seniors, 1955-1960 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Special departmental major, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Survey, intensive majors (office of educational research), 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - History 90, students, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Special students, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Fulbright, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Fulbright, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Woodrow Wilson, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - YC enrollments, 1973-1979 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Yale College majors, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - History grades, 1972-1977 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Early concentration for 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Directed studies for 1981-1982, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Yale summer programs, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Student advisory committee, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Affirmative action, 1972-1975 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Fair employment, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 24)